亲爱的  看看我的最新发明的装饰作品
Hey, honey. Check out my latest innovation in tree decorating.
我在树下安装了旋转个底座
I built a base that turns the tree
装饰树的树的时候就更便捷啦
so you can decorate it easier.
我命名为 "旋转树" [Lasy-susan的变体]
I call it "The Tree-zy Susan".
是滴  就在木匠店忙活三周而已
Yep. After just three weeks in the wood shop,
老爸就花了5分钟刮胡子  其他时间都用来装饰啦
Dad has shaved five minutes off our decorating time.
妈咪  我想好圣诞愿望啦
I finished my Christmas wish list, Mommy.
实现圣诞愿望的技巧在于
The trick to getting what you really want for Christmas
首先索要那种不可能得到的东西
s to first ask for the impossible.
我也时不时地喊两声"妈咪"  讨好一下
I throw in a "Mommy" or two to grease the wheels.
我就想要一件东西  妈咪
I only want one thing, Mommy.
地球和平  人类善良
Peace on earth, good will toward men.
抱歉  那好像是两件事
[Sighs] Sorry, I guess that's two things.
把它们包起来然后放到树下是有点难哈
Well, they're a little tough to wrap and put under the tree.
你还有啥愿望
What else is on your list?
我没想过还要什么备选项
Well, I didn't think I'd need a backup,
但我想
but I guess I could settle for...
龙鸣号遥控直升机也行
The Screaming Dragon remote pilot helicopter
内置1300万像素摄像头
with a built-in 13-megapixel camera.
有点儿贵啊
Well, they're kind of expensive.
但我们能给你买下那架飞机
But I think we can get you that helicopter.
这就是你怎么搞定滴  儿子
That's how you get 'er done, son.
拜托  让帕克以为他在耍我们
Oh, please. Letting Parker think he's "working us".
已经成为圣诞惯例
Has become a Christmas tradition.
去年他求我们把臭氧层空洞补上
Last year he asked us to fill in the hole in the ozone layer.
他得到一辆自行车
He got a bike.
到底啊  一架直升飞机
Seriously? A helicopter?
15分钟之内他就弄坏了
He's just gonna break it in the first 15 minutes.
还不如把钱扔进马桶里冲掉
May as well flush your money down the toilet.
哦  等等  你不能
Oh, wait, you can't.
他的遥控潜水艇已经堵住了
His remote control submarine already clogged it.
嗯  我刚刚没想到这一点
Mm, I hadn't thought about that.
马桶潜水行动是为了搜索救援
Operation toilet dive was a search and rescue mission
前天我冲进马桶里的玩具
for the action figure I flushed the day before.
一个都不能少哦
Never leave a man behind.
这些对你一点帮助都没有
Yeah, you're not helping your case here.
我不想说  但是我觉得乔伊说的对
I hate to say it, but I think Joey's right.
你年纪太小了而这个玩具又太复杂
You're just too young for such a sophisticated toy.
现在圣诞节我最想要的就是复仇
All I want for Christmas now is revenge.
还有那架直升机
And the helicopter.
还有地球和平之类的吧  但最重要的是复仇
And the peace on earth stuff, but mostly revenge.
还有那架飞机
And the helicopter.
老爸  你看看  乔伊把圣诞节给毁了
Dad, come on. Joey's ruining Christmas.
帮帮我
Do something.
哥们儿  我现在有点忙
I'm a little tied up right now, buddy.